wow-dps.com 2019-04-22

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which WoW-DPS.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.WoW-DPS.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by WoW-DPS.com.

###### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address, 

Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.

We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

###### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

###### Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

###### How we use collected information

WoW-DPS.com collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * _To improve our Site_  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
  * _To send periodic emails_ We do not sell, rent, or lease our customer lists to third parties. Member emails are used to send activation links, site updates and violation notices. You will NEVER receive spam emails from WoW-DPS.com.

###### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

###### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website\'s own terms and policies.

###### Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google\'s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

###### Compliance with children\'s online privacy protection act

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

###### Changes to this privacy policy

WoW-DPS.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

###### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [terms of service](http://www.wow-dps.com/index.php?=tos). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

###### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

WoW-DPS.com

www.WoW-DPS.com

admin@WoW-DPS.com
